■
掃碼加入我們
網絡翻譯愛好者聯盟
本字幕由網絡興趣愛好者翻譯完成
首發於字幕組網站  ZiMuZu.io
歡迎大家指正糾錯  共同進步
■
翻譯：lenin722  鍾意旻
翻譯： 嘟咖   薛定諤的貓抓板
校對：愛可歆的康納
時間軸：沒人
後期：普羅米修斯 大紅
總監：咖啡
CN
內容價值網絡（Content Value Network）
非常感謝CVN項目方提供CVNT數字貨幣獎勵支持CVN.io
本字幕僅供交流學習之用    所產生的任何糾紛請自行承擔
歡迎更多網絡翻譯愛好者加入我們聯盟一起學習交流進步
這樣吧  穿這個  唇色用酒紅色
I'm thinking, with this, if we have burgundy lips,
你知道吧  頭髮往後梳緊
you know, hair pulled back tight...
-用銀色可以嗎  -好的  我明白了
-Can I get the silver? Okay, okay. I got it.
你  好吧  可以了
You... Okay. All right.
你好  賈斯汀  抱歉打擾你
Hey, Justin, sorry to bother you.
我其實在研究薇薇安的裙子
I was actually looking at some of Vivian's dresses,
然後我畫了一些草圖  你可以幫我看一下嗎
and I drew up some sketches I'd love for you to take a look at.
你幹好自己的本職工作就好
Please just stick to the chart.
好的  但是我覺得這個點子很棒
Okay, but they're, like, cool ideas.
就是  我是說  我想
Just... I mean, I think.
-聽我說說  -親
-Just hear me out. -Honey,
我們請你來不是讓你來思考的
we're not paying you to think.
大家好  我們很榮幸
Hey, everyone, it's our pleasure
邀請到薇薇安 陳重返洛杉磯時裝周
to welcome Vivian Chan back to Fashion Week Los Angeles.
好了
Okay.
繼續吧
Keep it going.
明白
Got it.
妝畫的不錯
Makeup went well. It had...
你知道的  這風格曾經流行過
You know, it had its moments.
蘇蘇
Suzu.
在路上了嗎
You on your way?
是啊
Yes.
我偷了兩大包化妝品
And I stole two bags of makeup.
你一定會贏這場選美比賽
Yeah! You are winning this pageant.
當然了  因為我有你這個秘密武器
Of course. 'Cause you're my secret weapon.
好萊塢大名鼎鼎的化妝師
My Hollywood makeup artist.
好的  愛你  開車不聊了  拜拜
Okay, I love you. I'm driving. Bye.
歡迎來到墨西哥
Welcome to Mexico.
謝謝
Gracias.
蘇蘇
Suzu.
瞧瞧我們
Look at us.
我比你發育的早多了
I grew boobs way before you did.
但是我現在還在發育期啊
Girl, I'm still trying to grow boobs.
那倒是
That's true.
明天選美的事幾點開始啊
Hey, what time do we start that pageant thingy stuff tomorrow?
明早9點
9:00 in the morning.
光是排練就整整花了3天
Then there's rehearsals for three days.
-然後還要試裙子  -蘇蘇
-Then fit the dresses. -Suzu!
在陽台
Balcony!
我餓了
I'm hungry.
歌莉婭
Gloria!
我最喜歡的小鮮肉
There's my favourite little dude.
-不算小了  你都長大了  -是啊
-"Little"? You're huge. -Yeah.
你終於回提華納了
You finally came back to Tijuana.
是啊  我還給你帶了禮物
Yeah, and I brought you something.
是什麼
What is it?
我的天啊
Holy shit!
噘嘴貓
Potty mouth.
這個我在好萊塢見過
It's the one we saw in Hollywood!
我還以為你忘了
I thought you forgot about it.
-我怎麼會  -我覺得你應該
-Come on. -Well, you should practice
跟歌莉婭多練練英語  別讓她白來一趟
your English with Gloria. Take advantage.
是她應該多練練西班牙語呢  這樣
She should practice Spanish. Maybe she won't
她就不會一開口就暴露自己是遜遜的美國人了
sound like a lame American.
他說的很對
He's right.
呃哦  姐姐  你好大的啤酒味啊
Guacala, sister. You smell like beer.
好了  弟弟  我給你做了土豆匯香腸
Okay, little brother. I made you papas con chorizo.
放在微波爐裡了
It's in the microwave.
你好  下午好
Hello, good afternoon.
在這裡簽名
Sign here please.
你呢
You?
不是  我只是陪朋友來的
No, I'm... I'm not registering.
我不這麼認為
I didn't think so.
你說什麼
What did you say?
-我就是跟她說  -你不能這樣跟我的朋友說話
-I'm just saying to her... -You cannot talk to my friend like that.
好了 蘇蘇  好  別放心上
Okay, Suzu. Yeah, vamonos.
-好運哦  -謝謝
-Good luck. -Thank you.
你怎麼總是喜歡跟人吵架
You always get into fights.
-如果我贏了  -當你贏了之後
-If I win this thing... -"When" you win this thing.
當我贏了之後
When I win this thing,
那我跟察瓦的生活將會大有變化
it's gonna be really good for Chava and I.
當然了
Sure.
就這樣  自然的眼妝加上個深色的唇色
Okay, so I went with a very natural eye and a dark lip.
修飾一下
Touching up.
就做了一點改動
Just a little different,
就完全不一樣了
but you're done.
好啦  我有東西給你
Okay. I've got something for you.
友誼手鏈
Friendship bracelets.
得了吧
Stop it.
這樣好幼稚啊
Like when we were kids.
戴好了
There you go.
我特別開心你能來這
Hey. I'm so happy that you're here.
你知道嗎  我本來覺得我
You know, I didn't really think
不可能再回到提華納了
I was gonna be able to come back to Tijuana.
因為我覺得我完全不屬於這裡
'Cause I always felt like such a stranger here.
但是你總是讓我覺得我在這裡是有家的
But you always make me feel like I have family,
所以我要謝謝你
so thank you.
傻妞  你就是我的家人啊
Girl, you are my family.
沒錯
Yes.
好了  我們得走了  準備驚艷四座吧
Okay, we need to get going, 'cause we got people to impress.
你來嗎
Are you coming?
真的嗎  好  小心點
Really? Okay. Careful.
我認識他
I know him...
別這樣
No.
好吧
Okay.
姐們  別說你沒看到他
Dude, tell me you saw him.
看到了
Yes.
乾杯
Cheers.
可以請你跳舞嗎
Shall we dance?
抱歉  不行
No. No.
好吧
Okay.
所以我們到底是來跟誰混臉熟的
So, who do we have to rub elbows with?
我們趕快行動吧
Let's get it moving.
那邊  就是他
Over there. That's him.
那個就是紹賽多局長
Okay, that's Chief Saucedo.
都說比賽就是他出資搞的
He supposedly finances the contest,
據說他會跟贏得選美比賽的冠軍上床
and they say he sleeps with whoever wins the pageant.
那你還想贏嗎
And you're still trying to win this pageant?
小妞  這只是個傳言
Girl, it's just a rumour.
-噁心  -你才噁心  小妞  我們過去吧
-Ew. -"Ew," you. Girl, let's go.
這個可愛的小姐姐是誰啊
And who's this lovely girl?
這是我朋友歌莉婭
This is my friend Gloria.
紹賽多局長管理著警察局
Chief Saucedo runs the state police.
那只是我的個人愛好而已
That's just my hobby.
我對生活真正的激情在於美的追求
My real passion in life is beauty.
不好意思  等一下
I... Will you just give me one minute?
我想去趟洗手間
I have to go to the bathroom.
檢查一下格間
Check the stalls.
裡諾
Lino.
求求你
Please. Please.
要什麼都拿走
You can have everything.
求求你
Please. Please.
都給你  要什麼都給你
Take it all. You can have everything.
你是美國人嗎
You're American?
想活命嗎
Do you want to stay alive?
想
Yes.
你沒見過我們
You never saw us.
過來
Come on.
紹賽多在貴賓區
Saucedo is in the VIP section.
你有10秒鐘的時間離開這裡
You got 10 seconds to get out of here.
跑吧  外國妞
Salte, gringa.
嘿  蘇蘇
Hey. Suzu!
蘇蘇
Suzu!
Suzu! Suzu!
蘇蘇
Suzu!
蘇蘇  求你了  快接電話
Suzu, come on, please. Pick up.
有人要刺殺紹賽多局長
...assassination attempt on Chief Saucedo...
天啊
God.
不好意思  不好意思  先生
Excuse... Excuse me, sir.
我朋友在裡面
My friend is inside.
你不能進去  你不能進去
All right, you can't come in here. You can't come in here.
-好好好  -走  走開吧
-No, okay, okay, okay, okay. -Go. Go.
你正在呼叫蘇蘇  請留言
This is Suzu. Leave your message.
蘇蘇  我在千年俱樂部對面的餐廳
Suzu, I'm at the diner across the street from the Millenium Club.
聽到留言到這裡來找我  好嗎
If you get this, please meet me here, okay?
提華納市安吉利斯醫院
Hospital Angeles Tijuana.
我想找從千年俱樂部送去的一個朋友
I'm trying to find a friend who was in the Millenium Club.
你朋友的名字是什麼
What's your friend's name?
蘇蘇 拉莫斯
Suzu Ramos.
稍等
Let me check.
沒有這個名字
Nobody by that name has been admitted.
察瓦
Chava.
是我  歌莉婭
It's Gloria.
你們什麼時候回來啊
When are you guys coming back?
是這樣的  蘇蘇的電話沒電了
You know what, Suzu's phone died,
她讓我給你打電話
so she just wanted me to call you
告訴你我們可能會晚點回去  好嗎
and tell you that we're gonna be a little late, okay?
跟她說我要從她的梳妝台裡面拿錢吃午餐了
Tell her I'm taking the lunch money from her dresser.
好的
I will.
-拜  -拜
-Bye. -Bye.
抱歉打擾
Excuse me.
我找不到我的朋友了
I can't find my friend
我需要你的幫助
and I need your help, please.
你得去警察局報案  填寫失蹤報告
You have to go to the station. Fill out a report.
是這樣  我昨晚在千年俱樂部
Okay. I was at the Millenium Club last night,
看到了那些行兇的人  我
and I saw the men who did this, and I just...
我真的需要你的幫助
I really need your help.
好吧  上車
Fine. Get in.
謝謝
Thank you.
說吧  姑娘
Go ahead, senorita.
昨天晚上都發生了什麼
Tell me everything that happened.
有一群人帶著槍闖進洗手間
These guys came into the bathroom with guns.
其中有一個頭髮兩側剃掉了
One of them had the sides of his head shaved.
還有一個眼睛是綠色的
Another one had green eyes.
等一下
One second.
我現在的位置需要有人替班  我這有個美國人
Twenty, I'm here with a forty-one. An American.
她說昨晚見過千年俱樂部的那些人
Says she saw the men at the Millenium.
我跟老大確認一下
Let me check with Number One.
好  等候指示
Copy. Standing by.
我們到了警察局之後
When we get to the station,
我希望你把看到的所有事情都說出來
I want you to tell them everything you saw.
快要到了
We are almost there.
我先下車取我的午餐
I'm just going to pick up my lunch.
再準備一輛卡車
Prep the other truck.
你好嗎  唐娜 露西塔
How's it going, Dona Rosita?
歡迎來到露西塔之家
Welcome to Casa Rosita.
他在裡面等你
He's inside.
我的祖父母在40年代建了這座房子
My grandparents built this house back in the '40s.
這是我哥哥
That's my brother.
他想賣掉它  但我想留給我的家人
He wants to sell it, but I want to keep it for the family.
你們應該搞錯了
This is a mistake.
我只是想找我朋友
I only wanted to find my friend.
你要是說謊  小心我揍你
You tell me lies, I'm going to hurt you.
聽明白了嗎
Okay?
我不說謊
I'm not gonna lie.
你是緝毒局派來的嗎
You with the DEA?
不是
No.
你口音像美國佬
You talk like a pocha.
你是幹什麼的
What's your deal?
我在美國長大
I grew up in the States.
我在這生活過幾年
I... I lived here for a few years.
我爸爸是美國人
My father is American,
他經營一家工廠  在邊境處的一家加工工廠
and he owned a factory, a maquiladora, here.
工廠在哪
Where's the maquiladora?
已經關了
It's gone.
你爸爸呢
And your father?
過世了
Gone, too.
那你為什麼來這裡
Then why are you here?
我只是來看望我朋友
I just came to visit my friend.
蘇蘇  蘇蘇 拉莫斯
"Suzu. Suzu Ramos."
這些東西我要替你保管一段時間
I'm gonna keep these for a while.
好嗎
Okay?
我可以幫你找你的朋友
I can help you find your friend.
但是你必須先幫我做一件事
But you have to do something for me first.
你幫我做這件事  我就幫你找蘇蘇
You do that, and I'll help you find Suzu.
你要是不老實  我就把你們倆個都殺了
You mess around, and I'll kill you both.
-說是  -是
-Say "yes." -Yes.
很好  靚妹
Okay, chula.
我們會成為很好的朋友的  我們倆
We're going to be real good friends, you and I.
你去過貝克斯菲爾德嗎
You ever been to Bakersfield?
貝克斯菲爾德嗎
Bakersfield?
是的
Ey.
貝克斯菲爾德  在加利福尼亞州
Bakersfield, California.
沒去過
No.
我老家是貝克斯菲爾德
I'm from Bakersfield.
我也是美國人  跟你一樣
I'm American, like you.
也在兩個地方長大  跟你一樣
Grew up in both places, like you.
卡車準備好了
The trucks are ready.
把揚聲器打開  聽我指令
Leave that on and follow my instructions.
好了  跟上來  小妞
All right, stay with us, pochita.
快開  跟上
Come on, keep up.
-別管紅燈  -什麼
-Run the light. -What?
趕快  跟上  別降速
Come on, keep up! Keep up! Don't slow down.
好了  前面拐角右轉
All right, turn right on this corner.
車停在馬路邊
Park the car real close to the curb.
拿著你的電話  來坡上找我們
Take your phone and meet us up the hill.
嘿
Hey.
幹的不錯  靚妞
Good job, chula.
車開的不錯
Nice driving back there.
吐坎  把遙控器給我
Tucan. The remote.
看著  小妞
Watch this, bitches.
看看這個傑作
Check this out, chula.
厲害吧
What?
別難過啊
Don't be sad. Hey.
那些賤人自找的
Those bitches had it coming.
她好像不喜歡燒烤
Seems like she doesn't like barbecue.
我們快離開這裡吧
Let's get out of here.
你昨晚去千年俱樂部幹什麼
What were you doing last night at the Millenium?
陪我朋友  她想參加選美比賽
My friend, she wanted to get connected for the pageant.
加利福尼亞選美小姐嗎
The Miss Baja California pageant?
對
Yes.
我們在選美比賽上有認識的人嗎
Who do we know at the pageant?
行了  想辦法解決這件事吧
Okay. Figure it out.
我們為什麼來這裡
Why are we here?
你說你想參加比賽
You said you wanted to be in the contest,
所以現在你參加了比賽
so now you're in the contest.
我  那個  我想要的不是參加比賽
I... That's... That's not what I want.
我想要的是找到我的朋友蘇蘇  這是我唯一想要的
I want to find my friend Suzu. That's what I want.
我們會找到你的朋友的  不用你廢話
We'll find your friend, chingada madre.
你可以用這個聯繫我
You can reach me with this.
別丟了
Don't lose it.
也不要關機
Don't turn it off.
帶她去報名  波羅
Take her to register, Pollo.
不用硬拽著她
Let go of her arm.
祝你玩的開心
Have fun.
把你的左側轉過來  好嗎
Can I see your left profile, please?
現在轉到右邊
Now the right?
很好  轉回來吧
Very good. Face forward.
姑娘們  讓我們歡迎歌莉婭參加比賽
Girls, let's welcome Gloria to the contest, please.
你見過我的朋友蘇蘇嗎
Have you seen my friend, Suzu?
沒有  我很抱歉
No. I'm sorry.
-洗手間在哪裡  -在走廊的盡頭
-Where's your restroom? -It's down the hallway.
好的
Okay.
我就不能自己去洗手間嗎
Can't I just have a second
給我點私人空間  可以嗎
to go to the restroom in privacy, please?
-你還好嗎  -我不好
-Are you okay? -No.
打擾一下  等一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
你是美國人嗎  幫幫我  我也是美國人
Are you American? Please, I'm... I'm an American.
我被綁架了  他們在追我
I've been abducted. They're chasing me.
你幹什麼  你們要幹什麼
What are you doing? What are you doing?
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no! No!
為什麼給我戴手銬
Why am I in handcuffs?
為什麼我會在這裡  這是哪  我可是美國公民
Why am I here? Where am I? I'm an American citizen.
我被綁架了  求求你
I've been abducted. Please.
你為拉埃斯特雷利亞工作多久了
How long you been working for La Estrella?
我根本不知道你在說什麼
I don't know what that is. I don't know what you're talking about.
我是來找我的朋友蘇蘇的
I'm looking for my friend Suzu.
她在千年俱樂部失蹤了
She went missing at the Millenium Club.
我叫歌莉婭 富恩特斯  我是
My name is Gloria Fuentes. I'm an...
我知道你是誰  知道你做什麼的
I know who you are. I know who you are.
你是歌莉婭 富恩特斯  1991年出生
You're Gloria Fuentes, born in 1991.
你的職業是
You're a...
化妝師
A makeup artist.
你是裡諾 埃斯帕扎的女朋友嗎
Are you Lino Esparza's girlfriend?
你根本沒在聽我說
You're not listening to me.
我是美國公民  我知道我的權利
I'm an American citizen. I know my rights!
我要求被帶到美國大使館去
I want to be taken to the US embassy!
領事館已經知道你的事了  歌莉婭
Consulate already knows about you, Gloria.
我叫布瑞恩 瑞奇
My name is Brian Reich,
是禁毒署的探員
and I'm an agent with the Drug Enforcement Administration.
這些加密的無線手機
Now, these are encrypted radio cell phones
只有埃斯帕扎和他的同夥在在用
that only Esparza and his people use.
誰都跟蹤不到這些手機
They can't be tracked.
現在  你告訴我他給了你一個
So, you're telling me that he gave you one of these
可他甚至都不認識你
and he doesn't even know you?
這是你嗎
Is this you?
我當時不知道車裡有炸彈
I didn't know that there was a bomb in the car.
是因為這個你才和裡諾混在一起嗎
Did it make you feel important to be hanging out with Lino?
-什麼  不是的  -我理解你
-What? No. -I get it.
你是個無名小卒
You're a nobody from nowhere.
-來自破碎的家庭  -不是的
-A broken home. -No.
你一無所有
You have nothing.
這時你遇到了這個狡猾的傢伙
Then along comes this slick guy.
他就像是在向你炫耀他很有錢似的
He's, like, flashing money around,
他在給你錢花
and he's giving you toys
-給你買新衣服  -不是的  不要再說了
-and nice dresses. -No, please.
-他來自提華納  你剛好也住在那裡  -不是這樣的
-He's from Tijuana. You lived there... -No.
和他在一起還挺開心的  對吧
He sounds like a fun time, right?
我與此事無關
I didn't have anything to do with this.
求你了  你一定要相信我
Please, you have to believe me.
-好吧  看著  -你一定要相信我
-Okay. Look. -You have to believe me. Please.
你看  你看  你看啊  看啊
Look, look, look, look.
你炸毀的那棟樓是禁毒署的安全屋
The building that you blew up is a DEA safe house.
-不  -看看他們
-Okay, no. -Look at 'em.
看看  看著這些人
Look. Look, look. Look at these guys.
-現在  三個禁毒署的探員  -不
-Now, three DEA agents... -No.
因為你而死了
...are dead because of you.
看看他們  看啊
There they are. Look at 'em.
-不  -看看他們
-No. -Look at 'em.
他們是我的朋友  是真正的美國人
Those are my friends. Those are real Americans.
我們可以  以恐怖襲擊  謀殺和縱火的罪名起訴你
We have you on charges of terrorism, murder, arson.
你知道你會被判多久嗎
You know how long you'll go away for?
三十年  四十年  五十年
30, 40, 50 years,
除非你幫助我們
unless you help us.
這是一個跟蹤芯片
This is a tracking chip,
把它放在電池槽內  就像這樣
and it goes in the battery shelf, like this.
你試試看
You try it.
來吧試一試
Go ahead.
繼續
There you go.
完美
Perfect.
就是這樣
Bingo.
你要把這個芯片
You are taking this chip
放在裡諾 埃斯帕扎的手機裡
and putting it in Lino Esparza's cell phone.
不
No.
不  請不要再逼我回去了  求求你
No, please don't make me go back there. Please.
聽我說  歌莉婭  我希望是你所說的是實話
Look, Gloria, if what you say is true, and I hope it is,
但是你必須證明給我看
you're gonna have to prove it.
所以  拿著芯片
So, you're gonna take that chip
無論如何都要把它安在他的手機上
and plant it on his phone however you can.
從現在開始  你不幫我們
Now, if we don't hear from you,
我就會告訴裡諾  說他那裡有一個禁毒署的間諜
then I'll make sure Lino knows he has a DEA mole in his group.
如果你敢從他身邊逃跑
And if somehow you manage to escape him,
我就會把你扔進美國監獄
I'll feed you to the US prison system.
歌莉婭  這是你的手機
Gloria, here's your phone.
在他們集體檢查時  要確保裡面沒有芯片
Make sure there's no chip in it when they gather for checkup,
不然這就是我們最後一次見到你
or else it'll be the last time we hear from you.
這是我的手機號碼
This is my phone number.
記住它
Memorise it.
他們會想知道
They're gonna want to know
你去了哪裡  所以
where you've been this whole time, so just...
就告訴裡諾你害怕了  逃跑了  好嗎
Just tell Lino that you got scared and ran away, okay?
你準備好了的話就開機
Whenever you're ready, just turn it on,
他會馬上找到你的  好嗎
and then he'll find you, okay?
給你打車錢
For a taxi.
聽我說
Listen to me.
有一場戰爭將在提華納爆發
There is a war going on right now in Tijuana.
你能否活下來  完全取決於你自己
Whether or not you survive is entirely up to you.
如果你幫我們暴露裡諾的位置  我就會把你安全地帶離此地
You give us Lino's location, I will get you out of here safe.
那我的朋友蘇蘇呢
What about my friend Suzu?
我是你和你朋友之間最清晰的道路
I'm the clearest path between you and your friend.
如果你還想再見到她的話
You ever want to see her again,
那就做好你該做的事
you better do what you need to do.
祝你好運
Good luck.
蘇蘇
Suzu?
察瓦
Chava?
嘿  歌莉婭
Hey, Gloria.
察瓦  你回來了
Chava? You're home.
你舊手機是怎麼回事
What's with your old-ass phone?
連遊戲都沒有
It doesn't even have games on it, dude.
別亂動  把手機給我
Shh, give me the phone.
把手機給我
Give me the phone.
歌莉婭
Gloria?
不要再關機了
Don't ever turn off the phone again.
歌莉婭  你怎麼了
Gloria, what's happening?
露皮塔阿姨還住在市中心嗎
Does your Tia Lupita still live downtown?
蘇蘇去哪了啊  歌莉婭
Where's Suzu, Gloria?
我姐姐在哪裡
Where's my sister?
蘇蘇會沒事的
Suzu's gonna be fine.
聽我說  一切都會好起來的
You hear me? Everything's gonna be fine.
我現在需要你去收拾些衣服
I just need you to go pack up a bag of clothes.
這樣吧  我和你一起去  我們一起收拾吧  快點
You know what, I'll go with you. Let's go do this. Come on.
我去給你叫車  樓下見
I'm gonna call you a cab. Meet me downstairs.
-好嗎  -好的
-Okay? -Okay.
你為什麼逃跑
Why did you run away?
我害怕了
I was scared.
你最好別對我撒謊
You better not be lying to me.
那是你兒子嗎
Is that your son?
不  他是我的養子
No, it's my godson.
求求你不要傷害他
Please don't hurt him.
你好啊
Hi.
多乖的孩子啊
What an elegant kid.
過來  過來
Come here, come here.
你有手機嗎
Do you have a cell phone?
好吧
Okay.
好的  好的  好的
Okay, okay, okay.
現在
Now,
你回到自己的房間去  好嗎
you go back to your room, okay?
這不是我的房子
It isn't my house.
回你屋裡待著  在那裡等著我
Go to your bedroom. Wait for me over there.
回屋待著  聽到了嗎
Go to your room! Okay?
我跑了一整天
I've been running all day.
幫我把靴子脫了
Take my boots off.
幫我一下
Please.
請不要傷害那個孩子
Please don't hurt the kid.
你要我做什麼我就做什麼
I'll do whatever you want.
請不要傷害他
Just please don't hurt him.
好啊
Well,
有件事我需要你幫我做
there is something that I need you to do.
你為我做事
You do that for me,
我自然會確保孩子的安全
and I'll make sure the kid's safe.
可以
Okay.
我們這就是說好了唄
We have a deal?
是的
Yes.
那你現在把衣服脫了
Now, take off your clothes.
什麼
What?
把衣服脫了
Take your clothes off.
繼續
Go on.
怎麼了
What?
裡諾
Lino.
我不相信那個女人
I don't trust that woman.
他們不會找她的  她是一個美國人
They won't be looking for her, an American,
是一個混血的美國人
a gringa.
你擔心禁毒署找我們麻煩
You worry about the DEA,
我擔心她反水
I'll worry about her.
魯本死了
Ruben's dead.
帶著這些錢去參加葬禮吧
Take these pesos for the funeral.
躺下來
Lay down.
當年在貝克斯菲爾德
Back in Bakersfield,
我還是惠特尼高中的學生時
at Whitney High,
我遇到了一個女孩  你很像她
I met a girl like you.
薩曼莎
Samantha.
那是她的名字
That was her name.
薩曼莎
Samantha.
她很漂亮
She was pretty.
和你一樣
Like you.
她不愛笑
Never smiled.
也和你一樣
Just like you.
歌莉婭
Gloria.
你要開車去聖地亞哥
Hey, you're gonna drive to San Diego.
到我發在導航上的這個地方去
To the address that I put on the GPS.
當你到達邊境時  你必須確保
When you get to the border, you got to make sure
你能直視海關的眼睛
that you look at the customs guys in the eyes.
別做傻事
Don't do anything stupid.
回來的路上給我們打電話
When you're on your way back, just call us.
我們會告訴你在哪裡碰面
We'll tell you where to meet.
你說過你不會傷害孩子的
You said you wouldn't hurt the kid.
那麼  就把他送走吧
So then, send him away.
求你了
Please.
這輛車會帶你去露皮塔阿姨家  好嗎
This cab's gonna take you to Tia Lupita's, okay?
跟著那個孩子
Stay with the kid.
察瓦  看著我
Chava, look at me.
我會找到蘇蘇的
I'm gonna find Suzu.
好嗎  我向你保證
Okay? I promise you.
別忘了繫上安全帶
Don't forget to put on your seat belt.
聽著  混血妞
Listen up, gringa.
不管任何原因
If, for any reason,
不管是意外還是人為
whether it's an accident or intentional,
如果你帶著我們的東西逃走了
you get caught running away with our stuff...
或者你做了別的什麼蠢事
Or if you do anything stupid.
我就會拿著這把刀
I'm gonna grab this knife,
像殺雞一樣把那孩子給宰了
and I'm gonna gut that little kid like a chicken.
知道了嗎
Got it?
知道了
Got it.
路上注意安全
Drive safe.
路徑導航為您服務
The route guidance will start now.
我在幹什麼  我在幹什麼啊
What am I doing? What am I doing?
早上好  早上好  今天怎麼樣
Buenos dias, good morning. How we doing today?
-沒事  我很好  -你怎麼了
-I'm okay. I'm good. -What's wrong?
你比沒事可好多了  你剛醒來
You're better than okay. You woke up today.
-你可真幸運  -是啊  你說的對
-You are blessed. -Yeah. You're right.
你知道嗎  明天可不是所有人都能擁有的
You know, tomorrow's not promised to anyone.
醒來本身就是最大的祝福了
Just waking up, it's a blessing within itself.
-你說的對  -但是看啊  女士
-You are right. -But look, ma'am.
我只是來這為你打氣加油的
I'm just here to cheer up your day.
但這些貓頭鷹可以
These owls right here will look at you
在晚上注視著你入眠
at night and watch you sleep.
-不用了  謝謝  -好吧
-I'm good, gracias. -Okay.
沒錯  繼續  把他們帶進來吧
Yeah, go on, bring 'em in.
女士  請下車
Ma'am, I need you to step out of the car, please.
請轉過去  女士  手背過來
Turn around, ma'am. Manos atras, please.
你好
Hi.
護照
Passport.
-歡迎回來  -謝謝
-Welcome back. -Thank you.
繼續直走  接近目的地
Continue straight ahead to destination.
熄火
Turn it off.
解開
Open it up.
-剩下的在哪  -在車底下
-Where's the rest? -Under the car.
副駕座那邊
On the passenger side.
進來吧
Come on in.
你把這輛貨車開走
You take the van.
都在這了
It's all there.
我要你給裡諾捎個口信
I need to get a message to Lino.
你在聽嗎
Are you listening?
我要你告訴他
I want you to tell him
吉米說  他的人裡有個緝毒局的間諜
Jimmy said the DEA has a mole in his operation.
你聽懂了嗎
You got it?
明白
I got it.
滾吧
Get out of here.
謝謝
Thank you.
喂
Hello?
在鬥牛場的停車場見  就在邊境附近
Meet us at the bullring parking lot, right over the border,
走坎特拉街的出口
and take the Cantera Street exit.
知道了
Got it.
好  我要給誰打電話來著
Great. Who do I call?
-喂  -我有東西給你
-Yes. -I've got something for you,
但我想先確保你會保護我
but I want to know that you'll protect me.
我說了  我會的
I said I would.
你在聖地亞哥做什麼
What are you doing in San Diego?
他們讓我幫他們運武器
They had me pick up weapons for them.
在哪卸貨
Where's the drop-off?
-鬥牛場的停車場裡  -在提華納嗎
-The bullring parking lot. -In Tijuana?
好  我們這就去鬥牛場
Okay. We're heading to the bullring.
我們要抓埃斯帕扎
We want Esparza.
如果他在那  就用信息給我發個ox
If he's there, send me a text message with the word "ox."
除非你親眼看到他  否則不要給我發信息
Do not send a message until you have visual confirmation.
我怎麼出來
How do I get out?
通往海邊的出口旁邊有個黃色雙開門  到這來
Get to the double yellow gates next to the ocean exit,
門外會有一輛特警車 他們會帶你出去的
and there will be a SWAT van on the other side to pull you out.
明白了嗎
You got it?
黃色雙開門  知道了
Double yellow gates. Got it.
那是波羅
That's Pollo.
留意下周圍的情況
Keep your eyes on the perimeter.
前面那輛越野車
Front SUV.
看到裡諾就立即開槍
As soon as you see Lino, take the shot.
這姑娘可能會被亂彈擊中
The girl could get hit in the crossfire.
我說了  開槍
I said take the shot.
小心  老大
Watch out, boss!
該死
Shoot.
行動  開始行動
Move in! Move in!
趴下  快走
Stay down! Move it!
不  不
No. No!
救命啊
Help!
接電話  接電話  快接啊
Pick up. Pick up. Pick up.
喂
Hello?
-幹什麼  -沒人來接應我
-What? -There's no one here to get me.
我沒看到人  外面也沒有特警車
I don't see anyone. There's no SWAT van.
對不起  歌莉婭  你得靠你自己了
Sorry, Gloria. You're on your own.
不  不
No! No!
掩護我  奇沃
Cover me, Chivo!
不
No!
奧馬爾
Omar.
快走
Go!
用榴彈發射器
Grenade launcher!
地面二分隊  別讓他們跑了
Ground Force Two, do not let them out!
小心手榴彈
Grenade!
在牆那裡把他們攔下
Cut them off at the wall.
靠
Fuck!
該死的外國佬
Pinche gringa.
那些警察怎麼知道我們會去那
How did the state police know we would be there?
你知道嗎
Do you know?
他們怎麼會準備的如此精密
How were they so ready?
他們居然有狙擊手
They had a sniper.
你這個小婊子
You bitch!
嘿  別叫她婊子
Hey! Don't you call her a bitch.
好嗎  她剛救了我的命  夥計
Okay? She saved my life back there, man.
因為她別無選擇
Because she had to.
聽說我  裡諾
Listen to me, Lino.
有人跟緝毒局通風報信了
Someone is giving information to the DEA.
-他說的沒錯  裡諾  -什麼
-He's right, Lino. -What?
吉米讓我告訴你  有個緝毒局的間諜
Jimmy told me to tell you that the DEA has a mole.
一個叛徒  在  在你的組織裡
A traitor in your... In your group.
這都是你的錯
This is your fault.
什麼
What?
我告訴過你要幹掉布瑞恩 瑞奇
I told you to get Brian Reich.
我確實幹掉瑞奇了
But I did kill Reich.
告訴過你要處理好緝毒局
Told you to handle the DEA.
那是你的工作
That was your job.
我們死的人算你頭上
Our dead men are on you.
是你害死他們的
Their blood is on your hands.
你要哭了嗎
You gonna cry?
我們從朋友那借到這個地方
We borrowed this place from some friends.
你看起來糟透了
You look like shit.
去找件衣服穿吧
Find some clothes.
他們這應有盡有
They got some good stuff.
我很幸運
I got lucky.
布瑞恩 瑞奇是誰
Who was Brian Reich?
你怎麼知道這個名字
How do you know that name?
你剛才說的啊  我
You said it earlier. I...
他是緝毒局的人
He's with the DEA.
那個混蛋
That piece of shit.
沒錯  但剛才開槍射我們的是警察
Yeah, but that was the police shooting at us.
不管是瑞奇還是紹賽多的人  都一樣
Reich or Saucedo's guys, it's the same thing.
都不乾淨    他們是衝著我來的
They're all dirty, and they're coming after me.
知道嗎  我曾經掌管整個提華納地區
See, I used to run Tijuana,
全世界最大的邊境區
the biggest border in the world.
所有進出的東西都得先經過我們
Everything that came in and out came through us,
這就是我們洛星幫
Los Estrellas.
但現在  紹賽多想從我這奪走它
And now, Saucedo is trying to take it from me.
你覺得我是壞人嗎
You thought I was a bad guy?
我只是以牙還牙罷了
I'm just playing their game, chula.
-那為什麼  -提問到此結束
-So, then why would... -That's enough with the questions.
到廚房幫忙去吧
Go help in the kitchen.
嘿
Hey.
我是伊莎貝爾
My name is Isabel.
開始切菜吧
Start chopping.
所有人上交手機
I need all your cell phones.
你在這做什麼
What are you doing here anyway?
你是裡諾的女人嗎
Are you Lino's girl or something?
他上你了嗎
Has he had you yet?
裡諾綁架了我
Lino abducted me,
他們威脅我  說要殺死我朋友的弟弟
and they're threatening to kill my friend's little brother.
這就是我在這的原因  可以了嗎
That's why I'm here. Okay?
我也不是自願待在這的
I didn't choose to be here, either.
他們威脅我的家人
They threatened my family.
他們佔有了我
They own me.
不要相信他們說的任何話
You cannot trust anything they say.
你的手機呢
Your phone?
給  你這混蛋
Here's my cell, asshole.
忘了你的朋友吧  歌莉婭
Forget your friend, Gloria.
沒人會來救你的
No one's coming to save you.
你的手機
Your phone.
我們只是在清掃房間
We're doing some housecleaning.
波伊托是這的僕人
Pollito here is the maid.
他很擅長清除這件事  你懂我的意思吧
He's real good at cleaning, you know?
好香啊  寶貝
Smells good, baby.
你的手機呢
Where's your phone?
在這
Right here.
好
Okay.
繼續切啊  歌莉婭
Keep chopping, Gloria.
切  切
Chop, chop.
好
Okay.
好  好了  快好了
Okay, okay, okay.
不
No.
嘿
Hey.
求你了  求你了  求你了
Please, please, please, please, please.
媽的
Shit.
好了
Okay.
你去哪了
Where were you?
你幹什麼去了
What were you doing?
我去廁所了
I was just in the bathroom.
發生什麼了嗎
What happened?
你就這麼猴急著要上床嗎
You couldn't wait to get laid?
你幹什麼去了  湯都燒乾了
What are you doing? The pozole is ruined.
找出那個間諜
Find that mole.
起床了
Get up.
走
Walk.
-你要帶我去哪  -就快到了
-Where are we going? -We're almost there.
停
Stop.
如果你再遇到  我們昨天遇到的事
If you run into a thing like we ran into yesterday,
你必須得學會保護你自己
you gotta learn how to defend yourself.
你得學會用這個
You gotta learn how to use one of these.
從它開始吧
Here's an erre.
AR-15步槍
An AR-15 rifle.
產自美國
Made in the USA.
按住這個按鈕
Press on this button here.
這個是彈匣
It's a magazine.
子彈  這些是子彈
La bala, the bullet.
子彈能解決所有問題
La bala settles everything.
把子彈裝進彈匣
You pop it into the magazine right here.
然後把彈匣裝回去
Then you slide the magazine back in.
上膛
Then you pull the charging handle.
這是保險栓
Here's your safety.
撥下去  解除保險
Thumb down, safety off.
撥上來  鎖上保險
Thumb up, safety on.
學會了嗎
All right?
這次你來
Now you try it.
快點
Come on.
你不會總是像昨天那麼幸運的
You're not gonna be as lucky as you were yesterday.
不不不  不對
No, no, no, no, no.
先卸彈匣
Magazine first.
很好
There you go.
你得扣動扳機
You got to press it.
好
All right.
頂住肩膀
Against your shoulder.
不不不  不對
No, no, no.
兩隻眼睛都得睜開  好嗎
You got to keep both eyes open, okay?
你得用視力好的那只來瞄準
You got to use your dominant eye.
因為如果不這樣  如果你閉錯眼
'Cause if you don't... 'Cause if you close the wrong one,
那你就看不到目標了
then you're not gonna be able to see your target.
重來
There we go.
兩隻眼睛都睜開
Keep both eyes open.
給你
Here.
再試一次
Try it again.
擊中那些酒瓶
Empty it out.
蘇蘇的事怎麼辦
What about Suzu?
我派了維丘在查
My boy Wicho is on it.
他是我的技術人員  能力一流
He's my IT guy, and he's real good.
他查過醫院和停屍房了
He's checked the hospitals and the morgues,
沒找到她  所以說明她還活著
and she's not there, so that means she's alive.
聽著  我說過我會找到她的
Listen, I told you I'd find her.
現在  我
For now, I'd...
我想讓你先去沖個澡
I'd like you to take a shower.
你喜歡嗎
You like it?
我們這是去哪
Where are we going?
裡諾
Lino.
Lino!
我們剛烤好
We just finished the barbecue.
太棒了  我餓了
Perfect, I'm hungry.
我給你留了張桌子  在那
I have a table for you over here.
見到你真是太高興了
It's so great to see you.
你看起來好瘦  怎麼不多吃點啊
You look really skinny. Why don't you eat?
你以前吃過烤肉嗎
You had barbacoa before?
不行
Nah.
肯定不如這個
Not like this one.
試試
Come on.
-給  -我不餓
-Here. -I'm not hungry.
你肯定餓了
You got to be hungry.
怎麼樣
So?
好吃
It's good.
只是好吃嗎
Just "good"?
我就知道
That's what I thought.
你就應該這麼吃烤羊肉才對
That's how you eat some barbacoa, guey.
這就對了嘛
That is what I am talking about.
我不客氣了
Let's go.
你知道嗎  我在這裡長大的
I grew up around here, you know?
一直到我六七歲的時候才離開
Till I was about six or seven.
我來到美國後還會時不時夢到這裡
I used to just dream about this place when I was back in the US.
我非常想回到這裡
I wanted to come back so bad.
你懂那種感覺嗎  就感覺像是
You know, I just never felt like
這裡是我的根啊
I belonged anywhere.
然後我和我媽媽被驅逐出境
Then my moms and I got deported,
但當我回來時  墨西哥人看我像個外國人
and when I was back, I was too gringo to be Mexican,
我看他們也像是外國人
too Mexican to be gringo.
所以沒辦法  我必須硬氣一些
So, I had to be tough.
我慢慢學會如何得到我想要的
And I learned to get what was mine.
總有一天  我要買下這附近的所有土地
One day, I'm gonna buy all the land around here.
打算在這裡建一個大農場
I could just build a big ranch.
靠這片土地和滿地的肥料生活著
Live off the land and shit.
嘿
Hey.
我們找到告密者了
We found the snitch.
大家都在等你
Everybody's waiting.
這婊子還挺有脾氣的
Bitch had it in her battery.
伊莎貝爾
Isabel.
洛星幫絕不容忍
Los Estrellas will not stand
任何叛徒和膽小鬼
for cowardice or treason con cualquiera.
別  不要
No, no.
別  別
No, no, no.
奇沃
Chivo.
不  不  別這樣
No, no, no, no, no.
讓我跟他解釋  裡諾  別這麼做
Let me just talk to him. Lino, no!
不能這麼做啊  不能
You can't. No.
讓我跟他說一句話
Please let me talk to him.
求你了  別攔著我了
Please. Let me go back.
求求你讓我過去吧
Let me go back, please.
不要
No.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
聽我說  小妞
Listen, chula.
有時為了生存  你不得不弄髒自己的手
Sometimes, you have to do terrible things to survive.
只有這樣  未來才會有希望
Tomorrow's gonna be better.
我保證
I promise.
睡一覺吧
Just get some sleep.
好受些了嗎
Feeling better?
今天對你來說可是個大日子
You have a big day ahead of you.
唐娜 露西塔來了哦
Dona Rosita is here.
嗨
Hey.
米拉  看這件
Mira, this.
這件配你會很搭的
This will fit you just right.
穿上試試看吧
Try them on.
-什麼意思  -這都是為你準備的
-What? -These are for you.
一切都是為了今天
Okay? For today.
你想從我這裡得到什麼呢
What do you want from me?
你到底想幹什麼
What do you want?
-冷靜點  小妞  -不  我沒法冷靜
-Calm down, chula. -No, I'm not going to calm down.
聽明白了麼  我想知道你到底要作什麼妖
All right? I want to know what this is all about!
趕緊告訴我  告訴我你到底想幹什麼
I want to know! Tell me what's going on!
嘿  冷靜點  你可是我的心肝寶貝
Hey, hey. You're gonna be my queen.
我要送你去參加  加州小姐的選美大賽
I'm gonna send you to the Miss Baja California pageant.
什麼  你說什麼
What? What?
不要  我不會去參加的
No. No, I don't want to do this.
不行  我真不想去
No. I don't... I don't want to go.
我不想再呆在這裡了
I want to leave right now.
-先聽我說  -我不聽
-Listen to me. -No.
想讓我聽你說嗎  我不會的
Listen to you? I can't.
我不會聽的  我再也不會聽你的鬼話了
I can't. I can't do this any more.
到頭來你就會
You're just gonna end up killing me
像殺了那個女人一樣殺了我  對吧
like you killed that other woman, okay?
不如你給我個痛快吧  動手吧
So, just kill me, then!
-我要離開這兒  -求你聽我說完
-I want to go. -Please! Listen to me.
我不聽  你放開我  你放開
No! Just let me go! Let me...
別擋著我  行嗎
Get out of my way!
有些東西需要你先看一看
There's something you need to see.
誰給你這個的
Where did you get this?
你知道拉斐爾 紹賽多是誰嗎
You know who Rafael Saucedo is?
到底誰給你這個的
Where did you get this?
我問你  知道拉斐爾 紹賽多是誰嗎
You know who Rafael Saucedo is?
知道  他是警察局長
Yeah, he's the chief of police.
是個腐敗的垃圾
He's also a corrupt piece of shit.
你朋友在他的手裡
He has your friend. Yeah.
那些警察在槍戰之後把她帶走了
The police, they took her the night after the shootout.
他們公然賣淫  辦淫亂聚會
They run girls, throw parties.
他們一直都在這麼做
They always have.
你到底從裡弄到這個視頻的
Where did you get this from?
維丘
Wicho.
他假扮成一個嫖客  警察就把錄像發了過來
He posed as one of the johns, and they sent him that video.
呵
Yeah.
他們要她參加紹賽多的聚會
They're offering her up for Saucedo's after-party.
那幫人把她都訂滿了
They got her all booked up.
她可忙著呢
She's all busy.
一整晚呢
All night.
我也不想給你看這個的
Sorry you had to see this.
你得做出決斷了
You can decide.
紹賽多是我的敵人  正如他也是你的敵人一樣
Saucedo is my enemy, as he is yours.
至於你的朋友
And your friend,
她今晚會去參加聚會的
she's gonna be there tonight.
同樣今晚也是把她撈出來的良機
Tonight's your chance to get her back.
該怎麼做
How?
紹賽多總是邀請選美冠軍參加他的聚會
Saucedo always invites the winner of the pageant to his party.
我要他單獨呆在臥室裡
I need him alone in the bedroom.
不對
No.
不對  你是  你是要讓我
No. You... You want me to...
我要讓他能有機會對你為所欲為
I want you to do whatever it takes.
這是能撈出你朋友的唯一辦法
This is how you get your friend back.
奇沃會全程協助的
Chivo will be with you the whole way.
現在
Now,
現在我要你記住我說的話  小妞
I need you to listen carefully, chula.
為了達成這個目的
For this to work out,
你必須相信自己生而為冠軍
you need to believe that you belong up there.
你只需要看起來自信滿滿就行了
You just have to look confident.
我這邊買通了裁判
We bought the judges.
甚至買通了整個場子
Everyone works for us now.
好好加油
Play your part.
歡迎來到加利福尼亞選美小姐現場
...Miss Baja California.
你能做到的
You can do this.
就當是為了你的朋友
For your friend.
最後留下的三個決賽選手是
Our three finalists are
瑪麗琳 馬丁內茲
Marilyn Martinez,
歌莉婭 富恩特斯
Gloria Fuentes,
梅琳娜 唐娜
Melina Dona.
現在讓我們揭曉
And now presenting...
第二名是
the second runner up...
台上剩下兩名選手了
There are only two contestants left
但只有一人能問鼎加利福尼亞選美小姐的寶座
and only one can be Miss Baja California.
第一名是
The first runner up...
當主持人說出你的名字的時候  裝得驚訝點
When they call your name, act surprised.
本屆加利福尼亞選美小姐是
The new Miss Baja California...
歌莉婭 富恩特斯
Gloria Fuentes!
好了  接下來這步最關鍵
Now, this is critical.
當你被宣佈獲勝時  一個男人會走向你
Once you've won, a man will come to you
帶著紹賽多的口信  邀請你參加他的聚會
with a message from Saucedo, inviting you to his party.
到時候笑著應下來就行了
Just smile and accept.
好啦  幸運兒  讓我們送上熱烈的掌聲
Okay, fotos, finalistas, por favor.
祝賀你
Congratulations.
-能聽清嗎  -能
-Can you hear me? -Yes.
準備好了嗎
Are you ready?
準備好了
I'm ready.
我會全程通過這個裝置提供幫助
I will guide you through this device.
這樣我可以聽到週遭的一切聲響
I can hear everything through it.
說話的時候記得大聲點
Just speak loud enough.
一旦你上了那輛車  我就沒法保護你了
Once you get in that car, we won't be able to protect you.
我們認為派對地點在羅薩裡多南部的一處房產裡
We think the party's on one of the properties south of Rosarito.
加利福尼亞選美小姐
Miss Baja California.
歌莉婭
Gloria.
我們有各種提供高級陪護服務的女孩
We have girls from all the top escort services.
找到紹賽多之後邀他進屋
Get Saucedo to invite you to his room.
加利福尼亞選美小姐
Miss Baja California.
別  叫我歌莉婭就好
Please, call me Gloria.
你能賞臉真令鄙捨蓬蓽生輝啊
What an honour to have you here.
您可過謙了  局長閣下
You are too sweet, General.
我想問一下
I have a question.
這漫漫長夜  您過的還舒服麼
How's your evening going?
或許還能更舒服一點
Everything is good.
小姐  請隨我來
Miss, will you follow me?
在這等著  過幾分鐘我帶你進屋
Wait here. In a few minutes I'll take you next door.
明白我的意思嗎
Do you understand?
我需要屋子的方位
We need that location.
-102號別墅  -收到
-Villa 102. -Got it.
保護好自己
Protect yourself.
祝你好運  小妞
Good luck, chula.
哦  天啊
Oh, my God.
我的天啊  我找到你了
I found you. Oh, my God.
我終於找到你了
I finally found you.
我的天啊  我以為你已經死了
Oh, my God, I thought you were dead.
他們傷害過你嗎
Are you hurt?
你還好嗎  到底發生什麼了
Are you okay? What happened?
他們  槍戰後他們把我帶走了
They... They... They took me after the shootout.
他們把我領進車裡  然後
They led me into a car, and...
我以為他們是警察  你知道嗎
I just thought they were cops, you know?
他們逼我做那種事
They made me do things, chinita.
他們給我說  不聽話就會傷害察瓦
They told me they would hurt Chava.
他們把我賣到淫窩裡
They sold me into the system.
還給我打上了這個
They gave me this.
什麼
What?
洛星幫
Los Estrellas.
是裡諾做的
Lino did this.
你在這幹什麼呢
What are you doing here?
不是告訴你在那邊等著了嗎
I told you to wait over there.
跟我進屋吧
Let's go next door.
不好意思
Sorry.
何等動人的女子
What a beautiful girl.
這件紅裙襯得你更美了
This red dress turns me on.
把衣服脫了吧
Take off your dress.
咱們喝點酒助助興
I'll get you a drink.
我跟你說了  把衣服給我脫光了
I told you to take off your dress.
你是不是聽不懂人話
Don't you understand me?
過來
Hey.
躺床上去
Get in the bed.
裡諾  這邊發現紹賽多
Lino, Saucedo is here.
惠州  榴彈發射器
Huicho, grenade launcher.
Lino Esparza要來殺你  我們要逃出去
救救我
Help me.
歌莉婭
Gloria!
蘇蘇
Suzu?
Suzu!
快走
Come on.
蘇蘇
Suzu!
Suzu?
是你嗎  歌莉婭
Glo? Gloria.
走
Go!
別動
Don't!
歌莉婭
Gloria.
打得好  小妞
Nice job, chula.
你這頭該死的豬
Piece of shit.
你算是完成任務了
You got to finish the job.
蘇蘇
Suzu.
你看
See?
我就說你會把你朋友撈出來的
I told you we'd find your friend.
伸出手來給他看看
Show him your hand.
你一直都知道她在哪裡
You knew where she was all along.
我做了我必須做的事情  小妞
I did what I had to do, chula.
我們都是
We both did.
兩隻眼睛都睜大看著
Both eyes open.
蘇蘇  我們走
Let's go, Suzu.
昨晚在一場激烈的槍戰中
Last night in a fierce gun battle,
尊敬的紹賽多局長被殺害了
esteemed Chief Saucedo killed
同時裡諾 埃斯帕扎
Lino Esparza,
洛星幫的匪首也被確認死亡
head of the criminal organization, Los Estrellas.
紹賽多局長壯烈犧牲之前
Saucedo died heroically,
還試圖解救數名女性人質
trying to free a group of female hostages.
吉米
Jimmy.
我不可羨慕你的處境  歌莉婭
I don't envy your position, Gloria.
沒有紋身沒佩刀  我幾乎認不出你了
I almost didn't recognise you without your tattoos and your knife.
上次聖地亞哥倉庫一別
You've changed a lot
可真是刮目相看啊
since I saw you in that warehouse in San Diego.
你是個倖存者
You're a survivor.
活著走出了槍林彈雨
Walking out of a shootout like that.
媽的
Shit.
這就說通了很多事情
Making it through any of the things
看你過去幾天的經歷簡直是
you've been through in the past few days is...
你想要什麼
What do you want?
我想要一杯咖啡
I want some coffee.
你來一杯不
You want some?
看起來你這一晚上可忙的很啊  歌莉婭
Looks like you had a busy night, Gloria.
你殺了一個黑幫老大  還有提華納的警察局長
You killed a cartel leader and Tijuana's chief of police.
用的可是你們的槍
With your guns.
像你這樣的人對我們很有用
Someone like you could be very useful to us.
在此之前你要先提供點好處
I think I'm gonna need something from you first.
我要求被立刻釋放
I want to be released immediately.
清除所有案底
Cleared of all charges.
還有一件事
And one more thing.
察瓦
Chava!
歌莉婭
Gloria!